way2webhost.com 2016-05-11

# Privacy Policy | Baidyanath

Information Collection and Use Baidyanath, hereinafter referred to as Baidyanathayurveda.in  
is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Baidyanathayurveda.in collects information from our users at several different points on our website.

**Membership**

  * Your name
  * Your email address
  * Your billing and shipping address
  * Your telephone number
  * The type of credit card you are using if applicable
  * Your credit card number and expiration date, or other form of payment

**Order**

We request information from the user on our order form when making a purchase. Here, is where a user must provide their contact information, like name and shipping address, and shipping information, like credit card number and expiration date. This information is used for billing purposes and to fill the customer's order. If we have difficulty processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the customer.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. We use both session and persistent cookies. Usage of a cookie from our site is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information. Cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users in the aggregate by analyzing popular areas and products to enhance future experiences on our site.

**Usage Tracking**

Baidyanathayurveda.in database tracks the traffic throughout our site. This information is used to compile overall statistics and is not recorded at an individual level. This includes IP (internet protocol) addresses, browser type, ISP (internet service provider), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and 'of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate. The statistics help us decide which products and services best serve our members and guests.

**Newsletters**

If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address to provide communications. Out of respect for our users privacy we provide a way to opt-out of these communications. Please see the choice and opt-out section below. On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send you an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though you can deactivate your account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature.

**Security**

Baidyanathayurveda.in takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via our website, your information is protected both online and off-line.

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - Secure Socket Layers (SSLs). While on a secure page, such as our order form, a lock icon appears on the bottom of your Web browser. When you are not on a secure page, no lock icon will appear.

If we decided to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

If, however, we are going to use your personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify you via email. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner. However, if you have opted out of all communication with the site, or deleted/deactivated your account, then you will not be contacted, nor will your personal information be used in this new manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our web site notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post a notice we will also email users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices.
